

LY SOPHEA

O Toul Pongro, Phnom Penh - Cambodia

☑ sophealee8100@gmail.com

% +855 89438100

SOCIAL

f Sophea Lee

@NuggetMaka

PROFILE

I am very sociable, I like talking to people and I like to think of myself as a group person while I believe that doing things myself is easier I do not mind being in a group project at all, I like learning new things and somewhat gain experience from it if I can and get to know new people, it's fine if they don't like me because I understand that not a lot of people will but if push come to shove and I have to work with them I will try to make things works on top of this once I figured out how things work I love sharing and teaching people about my interest if they want my help of course.

SKILLS

- Language Fluency
- Communication
- Emotional Intelligence

EXPERIENCE

SERVICE | Park Cafe

Waiter

From 2021 to 2021

While I only worked at park cafe for only around two months I did learn how to serve the customer how to hold the tray and kept things tidy I wasn't very experienced at serving the foods and there was a mistake that was made but I try to learn from them and tried my best to not let it happen again even if it going to take a few tries. I ended up resigning from the job due to the resurgence of covid

DELIVERY | FoodPanda

Delivery Person

From 2020 to 2021

During my work in food panda, i learned most of the layout of the city I studied how to navigate the app and how it works and i also learned about how valuable time is to the customer and minute of different do matter

EDUCATION

DEPARTMENT OF ENGLISH

IFL

2020 - PRESENT

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Milky Way School 2013 - 2020

LANGUAGES

English

Khmer

INTERESTS

Music Audio Book Gaming Movie